Hunger Action Network of New York State; Records apap161
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Hunger Action Network of New York State Records1979-2003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Hunger Action Network of New York State
apap161
12.28 cubic ft.
The Hunger Action Network of New York State was founded at the Food, Famine and Federalism conference on May 20th, 1982. The statewide membership organization is comprised of direct food providers, advocates, and others with the same goal of ending hunger and poverty in New York State. Today, HANNYS has more than 200 member organizations fighting in unison. The organization holds offices in New York City and Albany, New York.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in the Hunger Action Network of New York State Collection were acquired by the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, in June 2003.
Biographical History
The Hunger Action Network of New York State was founded at the Food, Famine and Federalism conference on May 20th, 1982. The founding of such a pivotal organization such as the Hunger Action Network of New York State has lead to significant impacts on welfare and poverty in the state of New York. The Hunger Action Network of New York State has been fighting for to provide assistance through its member organizations for those in need.
The organization reaches communities in all type of environments, rural, suburban and urban communities that need assistance. The Hunger Action Network of New York State has been a pivotal grassroots organization. The Hunger action Network of New York States membership spans the population of the whole state, along with lasting effects on federal legislation.
Within the collection are press releases, lobbying and advocacy fact sheets, and publications. Thee publications and reports are both from HANNYS as an organization as well as publications that were collected by HANNYS for research purposes. Hunger Action, the official newsletter of the Hunger Action Network of New York State is a quarterly publication starting in 1984, the name changes in November 1997 to Grassroots, however we do not have a complete run of this newsletter.
The welfare reform campaign series is of interest to researchers for it tracks the organization by each campaign that the Hunger Action Network of New York State participated in. The series is arranged by campaign and within each campaign chronologically. Some of the campaigns are Hunger Awareness Day, HANDS across Albany, Feast for Famine, World Hunger Day, and the federal campaign, Welfare to Work.
Scope and Contents
The Hunger Action Network of New York State records documents nearly twenty years worth of grassroots activism providing New Yorkers who struggle with poverty and hunger a platform to stand on. Birthed out of a conference on the state of poverty and hunger in New York, the Hunger Action Network of New York state has hit the ground running and has yet to stop fighting and assisting New Yorkers and its member organizations. The materials cover many topics pertaining to welfare and poverty at the local, state, and federal level.
The collection contains materials relating to the social activism projects, its arrangement of administrative files, legislative and lobbying, news clippings, welfare reform campaigns, publication and reports, and research and subject files. The collection contains materials from 1979 to 2003. However the bulk of the materials are from the mid- 1980s to the early 2000s.
Within the collection are press releases, lobbying and advocacy fact sheets, and publications. Thee publications and reports are both from HANNYS as an organization as well as publications that were collected by HANNYS for research purposes. Hunger Action, the official newsletter of the Hunger Action Network of New York State is a quarterly publication starting in 1984, the name changes in November 1997 to Grassroots, however we do not have a complete run of this newsletter.
The welfare reform campaign series is of interest to researchers for it tracks the organization by each campaign that the Hunger Action Network of New York State participated in. The series is arranged by campaign and within each campaign chronologically. Some of the campaigns are Hunger Awareness Day, HANDS across Albany, Feast for Famine, World Hunger Day, and the federal campaign, Welfare to Work.
Arrangement of the Collection
This collection has no series.
Social Activists and Public Advocates; Hunger and Poverty; Welfare Reform; Files by subject; Clippings; Correspondence; Hunger Action Network of New York State
- Administrative, 1973-2000, Undated; 1; 1.66 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  The Administrative series is arranged chronologically.
  The administrative files of the Hunger Action Network of New York State cover the day to day dealing of the organization. In this series are conference, materials, photographs, direct mailings, and milestone anniversary materials. HANNYS has a long track record of social activism within New York State, the administrative series touches on many of the key issues that the organization fights tirelessly to eliminate.
  - FEMA, 1986-2002 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 2)
  - Court Papers, 1987; 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1987-1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 4)
  - Westchester Coalition of Food Pantries and Soup Kitchens, 1987-1989; 1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 5)
  - Department of Social Services Monitoring, 1987-1988; 1990-1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 6)
  - HANNYS Board, 1988; 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 7)
  - Documentation/ Verification Requirements, 1988- 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 8)
  - 6th, 8th, 9th, and 12th Annual Membership Conference, 1988; 1990; 1991; 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 9)
  - New York City Coalition Against Hunger, 1988-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 10)
  - Volunteer Services, 1989; 1993-1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 11)
  - Organizational Structure, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 12)
  - North Country Conference, 1989-1990; 1993; 1996; 1998; 2000 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 13)
  - NYS Department of Social Services Notes and General Information, 1991-1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 14)
  - Bank and Bookstore Sponsors, 1991; 1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 15)
  - Board Meeting Minutes and Related Newspaper Clippings, 1991-1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 16)
  - Department of Social Services Legislature, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 17)
  - Staff Meetings, 1991-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 18)
  - HANNYS Facts, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 19)
  - Feast for Famine Invitation, 1992; 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 20)
  - Halloween Protest, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 21)
  - Video Script, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 22)
  - Internships and Campus Work, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 23)
  - Letter of Agreement/ Advertising Contracts, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 24)
  - 10th Anniversary [1 of 2], 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 25)
  - 10th Anniversary [2 of 2], 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 26)
  - 10th Anniversary Advertising Agreement, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative), Folder 27)
  - Valentine's Day Dinner to Help End Hunger, 1993; 1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 1)
  - Membership Renewal and Newsletters, 1993; 1994; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 2)
  - Living Conditions for Minimum Wage, 1993; 1999 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 3)
  - 11th and 12th Annual Conference, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 4)
  - Welfare Reform Jobs 1st Bill, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 5)
  - Grant Proposal from Holding Our Own, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 6)
  - Southern Tier Regional Anti- Hunger Conference, 1994; 1998 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 7)
  - Hudson Valley Anti-Hunger Conference, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 8)
  - Capital District Anti-Hunger Conference, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 9)
  - 13th, 15th, 18th Annual Conference, 1995; 1997; 2000 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 10)
  - Community Economic Development, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 11)
  - HANNYS Employees, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 12)
  - Poverty and Public Policy Conference, 1996 (Box 2 (1-Administrative), Folder 13)
  - Hunger Curriculum, 1996-1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 1)
  - Opening Doors Diversity Workshop for HANNYS Employees, 1996 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 2)
  - HANNYS Office Papers, 1997 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 3)
  - Action Guide for HANNYS Members, 1997 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 4)
  - Mental Health, 1997-1998; 2000 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 5)
  - Hunger Action Network of New York State Direct Mailings, 1997; 1998; 1999; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 6)
  - Fifteen Years Working to End Hunger Anniversary, 1997 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 7)
  - Census of Emergency Food Relief Organizations Statistics, 1997 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 8)
  - HANNYS Membership Workshop, 1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 9)
  - Food Bank of Central New York, 1998-2000 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 10)
  - Eastern Region Hunger Summit, 1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 11)
  - Genesee Valley Regional Anti-Hunger Conference, 1998 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 12)
  - Nutrition Consortium of NYS Program, 1999; 2002 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 13)
  - Health Care Reform Act, 2000 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 14)
  - Plattsburgh Anti-Hunger Conference, 2000 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 15)
  - Syracuse Conference, 2000 (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 16)
  - Holiday Card, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 17)
  - How to Organize a Regional Anti-Hunger Conference, Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative), Folder 18)
- Legislative & Lobbying, 1973-2000, Undated; 2; 1 cubic ft.
  The Legislative and lobbying series is arranged chronologically.
  The legislative and lobbying series follows the Hunger Action Network of New York States history with the state government of New York. The Hunger Action of New York State was active in legislative advocacy. There are two folders in this series that touch on hunger in other states. The lobbying and advocacy are at the heart of this series. Much of the materials focus on promoting the state of hunger and poverty in the state, HANNYS achieved this by advocating and lobbying for those who could not do it themselves.
  - Hunger In Other States, 1981; 1984-1988; 1991 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 1)
  - Legislative Advocacy, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 2)
  - HANNYS: New York City, 1984-1988 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 3)
  - Legislative Advocacy and Research, ca. 1985 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 4)
  - Hunger In Other States, 1986-1988 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 5)
  - Legislative Advocacy, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 6)
  - Up and Out of Poverty, 1986; 1988-1990; 1993 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 7)
  - Community Action Agency of Franklin County, 1987 October 6 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 8)
  - Legislative Advocacy, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 9)
  - Legislative Advocacy, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 10)
  - HANNYS: New York City, 1989-1991; 1995-1996 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 11)
  - Legislative Advocacy, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 12)
  - Legislative Advocacy, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 13)
  - Legislative Advocacy, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 14)
  - Legislative Senate Survey, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 15)
  - New York State Budget Welfare Proposals, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 16)
  - Welfare Advocacy and Research for New York State Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 17)
  - Welfare Negotiation Proposals for New York State Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 18)
  - Welfare Reform Research for New York State Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 19)
  - Legislative Draft, 1997 November 11 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 20)
  - Legislative Draft, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 21)
  - Corporate Welfare Legislation, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 22)
  - HANNYS: New York City, 1998 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 23)
  - Lobby Day, 1999 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 24)
  - New York State Budget Analysis, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 25)
  - New York State Welfare Reform Work Study, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 26)
  - Lobby/Advocacy Day, 2000 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 27)
  - Farm Bill and Federal Food Stamp Research, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 28)
  - Lobbying and Advocacy Research State and Federal, 2001-2002 (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 29)
  - Lobbying Day Lobbying Tips, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative & Lobbying), Folder 30)
- News Clippings & Press Releases, 1973-2000, Undated; 3; 0.8 cubic ft.
  The News Clippings and Press Releases series is arranged chronologically.
  The News Clippings and Press Releases are compiled of news clippings from newspapers from New York State and press releases from the organization. Many of the newspapers included are the New York Times, The Times Union, The Daily Gazette, and The Troy Record. It shows a mix of nationally read newspapers as well as newspapers from the capital region. The kinds of clippings that are represented are rallies, protests that the organization HANNYS participated in or organized. The former executive director, Mark Dunlea and former associate director, Rachel Leon have many editorials and opinion pieces within this series.
  - News Clippings, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1991 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1991 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 8)
  - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1992 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1992 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 1992 (Box 1 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1993 (Box 2 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1993 (Box 2 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 2)
  - Press Releases, 1993 (Box 2 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1994 (Box 2 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1994 (Box 2 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1995 (Box 3 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1995 (Box 3 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1995 (Box 3 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1996 (Box 3 (3-News Clippings & Press Releases), Folder 4)
- Welfare Reform Campaigns, 1973-2000, Undated; 4; 2.66 cubic ft.
  The Welfare Reform Campaign series is arranged alphabetically by campaign and within each campaign the materials are arranged chronologically.
  The Welfare Reform Campaign series is a compiling of campaigns that were organized by the Hunger Action Network of New York State, other member organizations, and the federal government. The types of campaigns that have been included in this series are President Clintons Welfare to Work program, HANDS across Albany, SNAP, and Food Stamp assistance. Among other campaigns, this series in the Hunger Action Network of New York State collection highlights the efforts made by the organization and their member organizations
  - Children's Anti-Hunger Poster Project, 2002 February 07 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 1)
  - Community Works, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 2)
  - Community Works Minutes, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 3)
  - Corporate Welfare Reports, 1995-1998 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 4)
  - Corporate Welfare in Other States, 1995-1996; 1998-2000 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 5)
  - Corporate Welfare: New Yorkers for Fiscal Fairness, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 6)
  - Corporate Welfare Reports, 1998-2001 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 7)
  - Corporate Welfare, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 8)
  - Corporate Welfare: Sysco, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 9)
  - Fair Budget Campaign Surveys, 1998 October 06 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 10)
  - Feast For Famine, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 11)
  - Feast For Famine, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 12)
  - Feast For Famine, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 13)
  - Feast For Famine, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 14)
  - Food Coupon Campaign, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 15)
  - Food Stamps: Vendor Guidelines, 1979-1984 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 16)
  - Food Stamps: Statistics, 1983; 1985; 1987-1999 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 17)
  - Food Stamps: Expedited Food Stamps, 1987; 1998 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 18)
  - Food Stamps: General, 1987-1989; 1991-1995; 1999-2001 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 19)
  - Food Stamps: HANNYS Outreach, 1987-1988; 1997-1999 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 20)
  - Food Stamps at Farmers Markets, 1989; 1994-1995 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 21)
  - Food Stamps: Client Intake Form, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 22)
  - Food Stamps: New York County Contacts, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 23)
  - Food Stamps for Noncitizens, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 24)
  - Food Stamp Budgeting, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 25)
  - Food Stamps: Worker Training Program, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 26)
  - Food Stamps: Clinton's Initiative, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 27)
  - Food Stamps: Electronic Benefit Transfer, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 28)
  - Food Stamps: Promotion, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 29)
  - Food Stamps: Training, 2000 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 1)
  - Food Stamps: Work Group Meetings, 2001-2002 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 2)
  - Food Stamp Requirements, 2001 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 3)
  - Food Stamp Study (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 4)
  - Food Stamp Study (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 5)
  - HANDS Across Albany, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 6)
  - HANDS Across Albany, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 7)
  - Hunger Awareness Day, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 8)
  - Hunger Awareness Day Interfaith Prayer Events, 1995 March (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 9)
  - Hunger Awareness Day, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 10)
  - Hunger Awareness Day, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 11)
  - Hunger Awareness Day Lunch Prayer, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 12)
  - Hunger Awareness Day Hunger Tour, 1997 March (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 13)
  - Hunger Awareness Day, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 14)
  - Hunger Awareness Day Celebrity Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 15)
  - Hunger Awareness Day Action Packet, 1998 March 19 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 16)
  - Hunger Awareness Day, 1998 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 17)
  - Hunger Awareness Day, 1999-2001 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 18)
  - Hunger Awareness Day Sponsors, 2002 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 19)
  - National Hunger, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 20)
  - National Hunger, 1986 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 21)
  - National Hunger, 1987 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 22)
  - National Hunger, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 23)
  - National Hunger, 1990-1992; 1994; 2000 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 24)
  - Snapshot: A Survey of the Performance of Local Departments of Social Services during October 1991, 1991 October (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 25)
  - Snapshot II: A Survey of the Performance of Local Departments of Social Services during May 1992, 1992 May (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 26)
  - Snapshot III: A Survey of the Performance of Local Departments of Social Services during January 1993, 1993 January (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 27)
  - Snapshot IV: A Survey of the Performance of Local Departments of Social Services during July 1993, 1993 July (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 28)
  - Snapshot V: A Survey of the Performance of Local Departments of Social Services during January 1994, 1994 January (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 29)
  - Snapshot Advocate Survey on Child Care, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 30)
  - Snapshot Survey: Child Care in New York State, Undated (Box 2 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 31)
  - Tracking Welfare Reform, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 1)
  - Tracking Welfare Reform, 1998-2000 (Box 3 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 2)
  - Tracking Welfare Reform, 1998-2000 (Box 3 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 3)
  - Welfare to Work: Memo of Non-Profit Assistance Corporation grant application, 1998 June 10 (Box 3 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 4)
  - Welfare to Work: Surveys, 1982; 1999-2001 (Box 3 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 5)
  - Welfare to Work: Programs, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 6)
  - Welfare to Work: Bills and Amendments, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 7)
  - Welfare to Work: Rural Welfare, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 8)
  - Welfare to Work: General, 1998-2000 (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 1)
  - Welfare to Work: Assorted Research, 1999-2000 (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 2)
  - Welfare to Work: Programs, 1999-2000 (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 3)
  - Welfare to Work and Obstacles, 1999-2000 (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 4)
  - Welfare to Work: Transportation, Undated (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 5)
  - Welfare Reform: "Opportunity Knocks" Program Summary, Undated (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 6)
  - World Food Day, 1993 (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 7)
  - World Food Day, 1994 (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 8)
  - World Food Day, 1996 (Box 4 (4-Welfare Reform Campaigns), Folder 9)